NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
What are you up to this time, Targun?
Drop your sword, Bala.
I did nothing wrong.
Osman Bey and I had a talk.
But it's obvious that you are off to
something else.
Targun!
Are you trying to save your father?
Or, to cause problems for us?
Traitor!
I told you'll understand whether I am
Azreal or the Hellhound, Osman.
The life given by Allah...
... can't be taken by anyone...
... but Allah.
What was written on that paper?
Aygül...
... it's a secret.
I'm done with your secrets!
Tell me what was written!
How courages you three are.
Leave us alone!
We shall talk one on one.
It's enough, Aygül.
I know how to make her speak.
I can't leave you alone with this snake.
Listen to my words, Aygül.
If it wasn't for the sake of Osman Bey...
... I'd chop her right here right now.
Gonca. May you two go back to Tent now.
I know your father is alive.
And that he is a captive of Nikola.
I know you are trying to play
games on Osman Bey.
It's good that you know everything.
I don't know what you are doing here
and what was written on that paper.
But I will learn.
But I'd like you to tell me these not at
a forest like a traitor...
... but at the Tent like a proper Hatun.
You are right, Osman.
God is the taker of lives.
But God uses intermediaries.
And he has assigned me to kill you.
Sooner or later, you will pay for my
brother Ayaz.
Sertaş.
If you want to die while standing, so
be it, Osman.
I respect that.
For Rome!
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill him myself.
Cerkutay is back!
Today is the day of Flatyos!
Sertaş!
My Bey!
Take your men and leave, Flatyos.
How magnificent!
How wonderful!
Thanks to Allah!
Osman.
My son.
Where is my son, Osman?
You can do it, my Bey.
Bismillah.
How wonderful.
Praise be!
I will give the news to our people, my
Bey.
Don't, Abdurrahman.
Don't tell them.
If people ask, don't tell them that I'm
alright.
I want to understand how they're doing
without me.
When the time comes, I know what to do.
As you wish, my Bey.
I won't hand you even a single Turk!
Just like I won't break the peace
agreement between us.
Get out of my way, Yalvak.
Osman is going to die!
Take him away!
Tell Nikola what happened.
I didn't break the peace agreement
between us.
Drop your swords, Alps!
My Bey!
Where is that dog?
I sent him off, Osman.
I sticked to the peace agreement between
us and them.
What?
You sent him off?
What are you talking about?
The heathen has gone...
... but his partner stayed, huh?
Know that I saved your life, Osman!
I saved you from death.
You wanted to kill my brother and me!
Don't barge in, Alps!
Don't!
You too!
One of us is going to die today.
Your treason must be punished!
A partner of heathens can't be friends
with the ones fighting against them.
So be it, Osman!
Those who seek peace and those who seek
war but nothing else...
... can't work together for a bigger
cause.
Which cause is that?
We'd like to know that!
I will act like I work together with those
Romans you call heathens...
... then I will kill the biggest heathen
there is.
And who is that person?
Which heathen?
Which heathen!
What's wrong, brother?
Brother, huh?
I know what you are up to, Savcı.
You need to back down!
Only for the good of Kayı...
Stop!
Enough already.
By the good of Kayı, you only mean your
ambitions!
Let me tell you that the good of Kayı is
Ertuğrul Gazi!
Right now, my father is on his death bed!
For this, Kayı needs a new Bey.
And that Bey will be chosen tomorrow!
Don' tell me you and uncle talked about
his with the other Beys!
You want to become the new Bey while
Osman is not here, huh?
Choose your words wisely, brother.
I'm doing what's best for our Tent.
No, you are not!
You are only making it worse!
You are going to bring the end of our
Tent!
Don't you ever try this again, brother.
As you wish, Savcı.
As you wish, brother.
Know that I'm watching you.
I'm both watching you and Osman!
I will make you remember that you have a
brother if you keep fighting like this.
You can't imagine what I will do.
Geyhatu.
Geyhatu?
While Geyhatu is alive, we can't rest,
Osman.
Yalvak Arslan.
Did you really try to kill me and my
brother in order to kill Geyhatu?
Don't expect me to believe that.
I had other causes as well but they were
no good.
I wanted to establish that state which the
Turks have been waiting for years.
And I thought you were an obstacle for
this cause of mine.
What changed now?
Now, Osman...
... maybe you will lay the foundations of
that very state...
... which the Turks waiting for years.
And the biggest obstacle before that
state...
... is me.
Your wound is too deep.
We need to go to Inegöl at once.
No.
I can't explain this to Nikola.
We are going back.
All of our men died.
How can we fight against them like this?
I said we are going back.
We are going back.
I can't see what's inside of your heart.
If you really think that you changed...
... I can't say that you did not.
Losing hope from a muslim...
... is not acceptable for a muslim.
Osman. Geyhatu is getting stronger.
He wants to take Tabriz from Ilkhanates.
The Emperor is satisfied with Nikola.
Even if he loses Kulacahisar, Emperor will
keep supporting him with new armies.
What I'm trying to say is that Kayı is
losing time.
When it comes to Çobanoğulları, before
the Mongols leave Anatolia...
... they can't sustain themselves.
Are you saying that...
... you want to be unified?
Yes, indeed.
These lands can't take this rivalry
anymore.
Just like you said, Çobanoğulları and Kayı
can't rule together...
... but if we don't unify now, there will
be neither Çobanoğullari nor Kayı.
Then...
... you won't stand on my way ever again
and try to stop me!
You also won't use my uncle and brother
against me...
... so that all of our enemies and Geyhatu
will be destroyed.
This is the only thing I want from you.
No, Osman. No!
Geyhatu must die as soon as possible.
Or else, both Kayı and Çobanoğulları
will have no future.
Kayı Alp.
You have a name now.
Kayı’s Bey Osman gave you this name.
He called you Kayı’s future.
I won’t abandon you.
I won’t leave you without a mother.
I’ll live for you.
You and the future of Kayı.
When will the meating take place, Bey?
It’s about time, Hatun. Be prepared.
If Osman comes, there will be chaos.
There’s a chance Selcan
will fan the flame.
You find out what they do with Lena.
It’s enough if you stop them
from slowing me down.
Once Osman dies, both
Selcan and Bala will be exiled.
Father! What are you saying?
Aygül! Since when are you back here?
Where were you?
I had things to do.
Why do you ask?
Were you actually sleeping
or secretly listening to us?
Were you talking about things
I shouldn’t hear in broad daylight?
Aygül. How long will
you keep acting this rebellious?
When will you remember
that I’m your father?
Once you start acting like a father!
Hit me, father!
Don’t be afraid!
Go away before I do
something bad. Go!
Come, son. Come.
This is the treatment your
mother gets until you can hold a sword.
Come.
Do you hear that, Dündar Bey?
She’s filling your
grandson with hatred already.
All because of Osman.
Osman took your son, then your
daughter, and eventually your grandson.
What is necessary will be done, Hatun!
What else do you want?
So that you don’t change
your mind, Dündar Bey.
Because I won’t.
I won’t.
Tell me, come on.
I’m afraid the trick we’re
playing with Osman will be revealed.
Don’t worry. We won’t act
before Osman Bey comes here.
Nikola wants to talk to me tomorrow.
About what?
If you allow me, I’ll go and find out.
Of course, daughter. Go and
learn. You’ll tell us what he tells you.
Of course. Then, If you’ll excuse me…
Of course, daughter.
Aygül?
Savcı Bey and my father will
conduct a meeting of Beys.
- What are you saying?
- How could they?
Would Osman accept this?
He wouldn’t. And neither will we.
Let them try and see what happens.
I’ll go to Geyhatu’s headquarters.
I’m his Head Bey.
He won’t doubt me.
Does this have to
take place tomorrow?
Geyhatu wanted to poison him.
If he did, he’ll want to check it.
If Argun Khan is dead, Geyhatu
will be the Ilkhanid Emperor.
I need to prevent that.
Otherwise Geyhatu and his soldiers
will destroy the Turks in Anatolia.
I will kill him.
Now, we have news for Nikola.
Should we leave?
No. I want to listen to
the rest of their plan.
I’ll attack Geyhatu’s
base with the rest of my Alps.
Will this have the
same fate as the İnegöl Conquest?
If Geyhatu survives,
none of us will enter İnegöl.
If you say that you swore to give up…
… that time’s running out…
… and you walk on the path of faith…
… then I won’t leave you
alone, Yavlak Arslan.
After all the things I’ve done to you…
You’re a brave man, Osman.
Those were settled up with.
You didn’t leave us alone.
So we won’t leave you alone.
It was in our destiny
to fight side by side.
Let’s go.
Let’s get that cruel Geyhatu’s head.
Are we friends?
Until the Turk’s enemies give up.
Praise be!
I’ve heard enough.
Let’s go.
Savcı Bey is here!
Peace be with you, Bamsı Bey.
Peace be with you too, son.
I was just sitting around the fire,
looking for a man to chat with. Here.
If we keep conquering these
castles, we’ll get used to sitting here.
What do you say, Bamsı Bey?
Will be dead by then, son.
You’ll be sitting in castles then.
Once my Osman comes,
I’ll return it anyway.
Son, we’re old. If I’m going to die,
I want to die on a horse.
- May Allah give you a long life.
- Thank you, son.
You’re probably aware of
the situation, Bamsı Bey.
My father may never
leave that bed again.
We’ll have to choose a Bey eventually.
We’ll face each other
with Osman eventually.
He doesn’t hide his intentions.
From now on, neither will I.
I want to be the Bey of Kayı.
Of course you do, son.
You’re entitled to it.
You know that Kayı Beys want
peace and choose me over Osman.
Look son, no one knows that.
I want something from you.
What is it, son?
If I become the Bey and
Osman doesn’t accept it…
… stop him.
How will I do that, son.
Standing in his way will do.
Standing in his way…
of Osman…
What If I tell Osman not to accept…
… those who move with the with
the words of potters and merchants…
… as your Bey? What will you do then?
Then, you will have
fanned the flame.
Is that so, Bamsı Bey?
Savcı Bey.
When will we make that decision?
- Soon.
- How soon?
- Very soon.
- Today?
Is it today?
[Bismillahirrahmanirrahim] In the name of Allah, the merciful and the compassionate.
May it cure you, my Bey.
So, they’ll conduct a
meeting and choose a Bey tomorrow.
They buried me already.
How could they, my Bey?
They did.
What will you do, my Bey?
Listen to me carefully.
I recognise this walk.
This isn't the walk
of a victorious soldier!
You couldn’t kill Osman, it seems.
What about the other duty?
I see. Cerkutay is still alive.
What did you even do, Flatyus?
What was your success?
Osman caught Yavlak Arslan.
And I took Osman by surprise.
And?
We fought.
I made Osman drop his sword.
As I was finishing him…
And then, Flatyus?
Yavlak Arslan interrupted.
He saved Osman and they teamed up.
We were between two groups.
What?
Yavlak Arslan and
Osman teamed up?
What are they up to?
What kind of a move is this?
If you allow me, I shall tell
you what they are up to, Nikola.
While I was unconscious,
my men took me away.
I returned once I was
conscious again. I listened to them.
Osman and Yavlak Arslan...
... will kill Geyhatu.
They might even be on the way now.
They will kill Geyhatu.
They must be out of their minds!
Do you really think they'll do it?
Is there any chance
that they could do it?
- It is Osman, Nikola.
- Right. It's Osman.
If he kills Geyhatu and
gets out of there alive...
... that wouldn't be
good, Flatyus. Not good.
I'll go and tell Geyhatu this myself.
By the way, we were going to
meet our spy in the Kayı Tent tomorrow.
You'll meet me in
the forest before I meet her.
I might give you new orders
based on Geyhatu's response.
Okay, Nikola.
Don't be sad, Flatyus.
This isn't your fault.
You couldn't know that
Yavlak would do such a thing.
Make them take care of your wound
and rest.
Yavlak Arslan and Osman.
Who could have guessed?
What will we do?
Once she gets away, you'll follow her.
I don't trust her.
What will you do, Bala?
We shouldn't leave the Tent to them.
I'll stay here. You should go.
Okay.
Horse heart...
Horse milk...
Horse tongue...
Horse...
Don't you eat things like lambs or cows?
Mongols don't carry anything that
they can't use as a weapon.
Those who go to war with lambs
and cows go slowly.
Talk. Why did you come?
I have some news
I think you'd like, Geyhatu.
Talk.
Osman.
He ambushed Yavlak Arslan.
My man attacked Osman
to save Yavlak Arslan.
To save Yavlak Arslan...
And Yavlak Arslan backstabbed
my man to save Osman, Geyhatu.
Yavlak Arslan(Lion)
is such a strange lion.
He's indeed a strange man.
Möngke. Your son Möngke, Geyhatu.
Do you know who he
teamed up with to kill you?
Yavlak Arslan!
Now, they teamed up with Osman.
They're coming for you, Geyhatu.
Small men are very ambitious.
Osman and Yavlak Arslan will come.
Geyhatu will make soup from their skins!
I like soups!
I want to help out.
May I kill a couple of Turks?
Let's write a letter to Kayıs.
- Our little Lord will take it to them.
- I'm honoured. What will it say?
You'll hear while we write it.
Now, leave.
Little Lord told me a lie and a truth.
His men didn't want to save Yavlak.
He wanted to kill Osman.
These fools allied Osman and Yavlak.
Now, they're coming here.
I'll turn both of them into soup!
- Don't disturb me while I'm eating, Kongar.
- Don't call me Kongar!
I'll skin all you Mongols alive!
I know that you want to die, Kongar.
But don't expect it from me.
If you call me Kongar again,
you'll have to kill me.
We used to call you that.
Kongar.
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ, what are you doing, brother?
Our Bey is looking!
We place Alps on this flank
and this flank.
Then...
You and I are going to get in
Geyhatu's tent.
We are going to take Cerkutay with us.
My Osman, I am okay to be martyres
with you, but...
we can't even get near of that
tent.
Yavlak Arslan, do you know how I get into
Kulucahisar all one?
I wonder how.
As a captive.
I knew they'd take me to Nicola
when they captured me.
- And that was what they did!
- Are you going to hand yourself in?
Yes.
I will.
But this time I'll hand myself in you.
In me?
- There is news, Nicola.
- About what?
- About Kayıs.
- What are these Kayıs after, Vladius?
- They are meeting to choose a Bey.
- Choosing a Bey?
While Osman is gone.
What happens if they choose a
Bey while Osman is not there, Vladius?
Osman and his Alps will deny it, Nicola.
That's right.
Geyhatu will kill Osman. Kayıs will be
messed up on choosing a new Bey..
And we will take what we've lost
back.
Are you a brave man, Vladius?
You say, Nicola.
Am I?
You are a man who can dare to go to
Kayı tribe all alone.
Is there anything else I should do
other than letting them kill me?
There is. There is.
You will go to Kayı Tribe. You'll inform
Dündar and Savcı Bey that we declare war.
Then they are going to kill me, right?
Vladius, didn't you want to die?
You know I am going to go there, Nicola.
I just have to make sure that this
is right for Rome.
A letter from Geyhatu to Kayıs.
This is right for Rome, Vladius.
- What does this say, Nicola?
- Beautiful things.
I like beautiful things, Vladius.
I'll tell you about it.
But before going to Kayı tribe,
take those clothes off.
Wear something decent to
represent Rome.
Let's see what Targun has done.
Targun.
What would you do if you were Osman...
and people gathered a meeting to choose
a new Bey, Lena?
I'd be aware that I wouldn't be able to
live here anymore.
So I'd do anything to prevent this from
happening.
So he'll do his best.
But the question is...
what can he do?
What's it, Selcen Hatun?
Are you lost?
Or are you searching someone to
insult?
No.
I've heard that Dündar and Savcı Beys
arranging a meeting.
Their Hatuns were absent.
So I wondered you.
Thank you, thank you.
We don't need to do anything
for now.
If you don't do something stupid...
we won't have any problem.
What can I say?
This is what I am.
You can't predict what I am going to do.
But if there is a meeting being aranged
while my Osman is absent...
I feel I must do something.
Selcan Hatun.
Aren't you afraid that...
something bad may happen to you
while Osman is not here to protect you?
May Allah prevent.
If Osman Bey's not here, I am here.
Who can do something bad to Selcen Hatun?
Don't push your luck, Bala.
So you say this is a new era, huh?
You think it'll be too late when
my Osman is back.
Okay then, I'll think of something
before my Osman arrives in here.
You turned Dündar and Savcı Bey against
my Osman.
You send the old hunter
to hunt a lion.
You troubled your Beys.
You couldn't see what a lion
is capable of...
when someone try to hunt him down.
I hope the best end for you.
Open the doors!
Boran, Göktuğ.
- Hide where I told you to.
- Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
Eyvallah my Bey.
Gence Bey, you are one of us now.
Take a good care of yourself.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
We'll fight with the sign of yours.
Eyvallah (thank you).
Yavlak Arslan.
Let's go.
May our holy war be blessed.
Yes.
Targun, the power that infiltrated into
Kayı tribe.
Is Osman dead?
- It's not that easy, Nicola.
- No, no, you are right.
Osman hasn't ever been a piece of cake.
Let's go there and kill all of them!
We can get rid of Nicola fast!
Wait, Aygül!
Wait!
Check it.
They are crowded.
Would Osman Bey let his cousin die
because of that dog?
Let's get the information and
go back.
This is not a simple infidel.
This is a big infidel.
I can just take his life and
be martyred.
Aygül, one thousand Byzantine
soldiers don't worth you.
Now our mission is to learn
what is going on here.
Eyvallah (okay) Gonca.
Let's wait and see.
Enough, Nicola!
What do you want from me?
I want the congratulate you at first.
You are getting married to Osman. I would
wish you kids, little Osmans, but...
this would not be good for me.
Yes, we are getting married.
You did your job well, obviously.
This was faster then I expected.
They are coming here, Aygül.
We must kill them.
They are two.
- One can shout.
- We silence them.
- One for you, one for me.
- Agreed.
Osman didn't get suspicious of you.
He did, surely.
So?
And I told him everything.
I told him that you abducted my father
and that was why I had to help you.
Good girl. You are beyond the
expectations! Good my little devil!
When are you going to free my father?
Targun, Targun, Targun!
This is not gold.
This is poison.
You are going to poison each Bey
in Kayı tribe, but..
but...
Do it all together, I don't want to work
on them one by one.
You can handle it, don't give me
that look.
Why? Because Targun doesn't want her
father to die.
Isn't that right?
Right, Targun?
It's right.
We shared them, Aygül!
I couldn't stop myself.
Come on Aygül.
Nicola is gone.
What is she doing there?
How can I do this to them?
I follow your path, my father.
I am striving for Kayı's future.
My heart is crying, but...
there is nothing left to do.
Brother...
if you hear us, you should know that...
our objective is good. We are doing this
to make sure that your efforts...
don't be wasted.
Dündar Bey, it is not good to
arrange a meeting...
before Osman Bey comes here.
If Ertuğrul Bey wakes up and hears all
about this...
he won't give his blessings to you.
You are talking like you know
my father better than me, Abdurrahman Bey.
Son.
I spend my whole life fighting with
Eruğrul Bey back to back.
We went to battlefield with my Bey
while you were not born.
Of course I know about him.
Welcome, Beys.
Nephew, let's go in.
Let's go uncle.
My Bey, wake up. Wake up.
Wake up and prevent this
disaster from happening.
Otherwise, it's going to be
bad.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of allah the merciful the compassionate)
With the 99 name of Allah, who is the
most powerful one, to whom we pray.
My Beys...
Welcome, Beys, Aghas.
Thanks.
Welcome to my Ertuğrul Bey's tent.
What is this about, Selcen Hatun?
Is there something important?
Yes there is something important.
Tell us.
I've heard that you are choosing a Bey.
Then yes, there is something important.
But tell me, Dündar. How are you going to
choose that Bey while my Osman is absent?
Aunt, you know the tradition.
Women are not allowed in meetings.
Yes, I know the tradition.
I also know that...
my Ertuğrul Bey is still alive.
He is alive but he is not healthy
enough to reign...
Don't talk too much Dündar!
I know the tradition.
I am asking to you...
isn't each son of Bey the heir of
Beyship?
What does this mean? You gather a meeting
in a hurry while Osman is away for duty.
Aunt, your opinions aren't valid here.
Selcan Hatun is one of the notable ones
in our community.
She has right to speak.
Yes, I do of course.
And I stand up for Osman Bey.
If Osman Bey is absent, I am here for him.
Walk!
- I brough the traitors for Geyhatu.
- Geyhatu wants to see them now!
Walk!
Make room for me Gündüz.
Here I am!
Is there anyone who can
throw me out?
Selcan Aunt.
Don't make me use force.
You can't touch me Dündar.
Hey, Dündar Bey, Hey.
Hey, Savcı Bey, Hey.
Hey Kayı Beys, Hey.
Kayı Beys...
You can do anything!
You are powerful enough for anything!
Bamsı...
But, but...
do you know what you can't do?
You can't touch Selcan Hatun.
Bamsı...
Ah Dündar Bey! You couldn't
throw that Selcan Hatun out!
Now that Bamsı Bey is here...
I call this meeting to end.
Bamsı Bey's arrival is no good.
Things will get messed up.
Savcı Bey was supposed to
convince Bamsı Bey.
Come on, Hazal Hatun. Who can turn Bamsı
Bey against Osman Bey?
Walk! Traitor!
Walk!
- Geyhatu will beat us down.
- Shut up! Walk!
Let them talk.
These are their last words!
Mongol's dog! I will kill you myself
as soon as I get out of here.
Osman, look around.
How can you stay alive out of here?
Walk!
Walk now!
What is this about?
What if Osman is here?
''Heathen! Leave our lands!
Leave here, you heathen!''
Stay calm, gentlemen. Stay calm.
I came alone. I'm unarmed.
-I have important news for your bey.
-Unmount.
Wait here.
Baysungur, what's this fuss?
Flatyos is here
He has important news.
He should wait. We'll find out after
the meeting.
No. We aren't in a hurry.
Let's see what he has to say.
If had the courage to come here,
it must be important.
Baysungur, bring him.
Let him come and speak.
Are you going to deceive us with peace
again?
On contrary, I came to declare war.
War?
You want war?
If you allow me...
...I should convey Gethatu's letter.
Geyhatu?
Why does he intervene?
Move!
He gave Kulucahisar, Söğüt
and Karacahisar to Nikola.
If we don't leave them in
three days...
If you don't, there will be a war between
Geyhatu and the Kayı.
Rome will stand with Geyhatu with
all its strenght.
If needed, of course.
And by the way, Argun Khan died.
Geyhatu will be the ruler of
Ilkhaganete soon.
So, you'll fight against the
empire of Ilkhaganate.
Enough! Enough!
Be silent! Be silent!
After we send him, we should dismiss the
election meeting and start a war meeting.
And Osman will manage the war meeting.
He is the only one who can do it.
-Osman?
-Yeah, Osman.
-Osman, huh?
-Osman, yes. Yes, Osman, kid.
Osman who I warned many times about this?
Osman who brought this upon us?
Do you expect him to bring us victory
against Ilkhaganete?
Will we fight with a country that has
a thousand warriors for each of ours?
Yes!
-Bamsı Bey!
-Savcı!
Bamsı Bey.
Savcı Bey, Bamsı Bey is our elder.
You will fight.
If we all going to die, I should skin him.
-My nephew!
We don't hurt envoys.
Don't forget our traditions.
Have you forgot that they stabbed me
on my back and tortured me.
You said what you have to say.
Now leave here.
Don't you wonder where Osman is?
Tell me where Osman is.
Osman allied Yavlak Arslan.
-Tell me the truth. How do you know that?
-Yavlak Arslan saved Osman from my hands.
And they are probably on their way to
Geyhatu's tents.
-Why would Osman go there?
-If I know Osman well...
...he is going there to stab
Geyhatu on his heart.
Hazal Hatun, how can your brother
Yavlak Arslan form alliance with Osman?
-I'm talking to you, Hazal Hatun.
-Enough!
Hazal Hatun, Hazal Hatun. I hear you!
I'm not deaf!
I brought you the traitors, Geyhatu.
No one can deceive Geyhatu.
Argun Khan died.
Argun Khan is no more.
The great enemy is defeated.
The poison worked.
Prepare the warriors.
I'm going to Tebriz.
Geyhatu will sit on Argun Khan's throne.
What will happen to Osman?
Geyhatu will be the great khagan.
You will kill the little beys.
While he is on his way to
the throne in Tebriz, you'll die here.
Just like Argun Khan.
Think, beys.
But don't forget.
You have three days.
-Saltuk!
-Yes, my bey?
Take him out.
Come on!
There is still no sign.
Something is wrong.
Brother, should we wait a little longer?
Come on now!
It seems that they are ambushed.
-They are ambushed, come on!
-Unsheathe, brothers!
Beys of Kayı!
The meeting is over.
Now, pray Allah for Osman to return.
And no one should do things
behind Osman.
We are here, Osman Bey!
Brotherhood of war doesn't
end that easily.
Brothers!
Victory belongs to those who believe!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar!
Geyhatu took his army and left.
And he set a trap for us.
He'll return even stronger.
Now, he'll return as the sultan
of Ilkhaganate.
Let him come!
So, Yavlak Arslan...
...you fought well.
-I'm glad to witness your fighting.
Flatyos, you'll leave these tents
safe and sound.
Turkic tents are the lair of lions.
Because even the unhonorable ones...
...gets treated with honor.
Tell the Rum lord Nikola,
we won't hand over...
...Kulucahisar, Söğüt
or Karacahisar...
...without a fight.
Not Geyhatu, even Genghis Khan
if he wakes up from death...
...can't ask us to accept that.
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akber!
Mighty Allah is my witness that...
...I've done everything I could...
...to prevent a war coming
to our tents.
To live in peace, to night fight
with neither the Mongols nor the Rums...
...I even took the change of
getting called a craven.
But, but,
if war is in our destiny...
...either it's the enemy who brings it
or it's my brother, I'll fight!
Neither I'll give you my brother Osman,
nor a crumble of land!
We, we came to these lands...
...and sacrificed our blood for these
lands. We aren't giving them back!
We came to these lands to build a state!
And we'll build that state!
Long live Savcı Bey! Long live Savcı Bey!
Go on!
Leave now.
The door of penitence...
...is it open for non-muslims too?
Göktuğ.
Inshallah.
Inshallah you will forswear and
become muslim, Cerkutay.
Inshallah.
So, Yavlak Arslan...
...what will you do?
-When Geyhatu returns as the khagan...
...all the Çobanoğlu tribe will stand
against him with their swords.
What will you do, Osman Bey?
The disgraceful meeting has ended.
The election of the bey is for tomorrow.
The bad days are over,
the worse days are there to come.
Tell us.
What does Nikola want?
What does he want from you?
He wants me to kill Osman Bey.
You what?
How will you kill him?
Huh?
It's Osman Bey's word.
When we marry, Nikola will be happy and
he'll think that I'll kill Osman easily.
However...
Osman Bey knows that I won't
do such a thing.
He knows that I just want to
save my father.
Osman Bey...
has done the right thing
by choosing you, Targun.
However, I have to save
my father.
Poison. You'll poison the Beys
in the Kayı tribe with this.
Do it when they are all together.
As Targun doesn't want her father
to die.
I have to protect my father.
Whether Osman or Yavlak Arslan...
won't come out alive from Geyhatu's tribe.
Ah, brother...
his greed causes him trouble.
We shouldn't make a choice.
I'll declare my Beyship tomorrow.
Nephew...
If Osman is alive and becomes an
ally with Yavlak Arslan...
he won't forgive you.
Your Alps can't set against Osman's Alps.
He comes and...
takes Beyship.
If the Beyship is taken, it
won't be given back.
If Osman is alive...
I'll take him to court...
because of endangering Kayıs'
peace.
What matters if he is an
ally with Yavlak Arslan?
Will Yavlak
Arslan stand against Geyhatu's army?
He sold us out to Osman...
and he'll sell Osman out to Geyhatu.
Kayıs will be in trouble.
So, you're decided.
So, you won't...
stand back.
May Allah give you power.
Uncle...
Is our agreement still valid?
Yes, it is.
It is.
Good.
What does it mean, Dündar Bey?
What are you up to? Tell me.
If my brother and Osman...
are allies...
it means everything has changed.
Calm down, Hatun.
Calm down.
Everything is just as I want them to be.
Tomorrow...
Savcı will declare his Beyship.
Bamsı and his Alps won't accept that.
Then, we'll get rid of Bamsı or...
Savcı.
What about Osman?
What about my brother?
Pray to Allah that...
I wish your brother didn't
raid Geyhatu's tribe.
Or else, nobody can save him.
I'll go to Kayı tribe tomorrow.
And I'll take the Beyship relic.
I'll make the Kayı Alps as one man.
Then, with Yavlak Arslan...
I'll fight Geyhatu.
Then, I'll rip that dog Nikola
out of these lands!
Eyvallah.
Come on.
From now on...
we are at a turning point.
Tomorrow, I'll be the Bey of Kayı tribe or...
I'll die.
Your Alps are with you.
You'll be safe and sound, my Bey.
Bamsı brought his horses.
Tomorrow he'll draw a sword to me.
I know it.
He can do anything to make Osman the Bey.
I informed Bayhuca.
If I die tomorrow, he'll protect our case.
No sleeping tonight!
They may act anytime!
Tomorrow...
be ready to shed brother blood.
My Bey...
Kayı tribe will fight itself?
Osman wants to kill
you to become Kayı Bey.
Your brother obeys our traditions, right?
But if our traditions let you kill your
brother in case of a state issue...
Osman will kill you.
What I am saying is that before
Osman kills you...
Enough!
- Don't ever talk about it again.
- You have to do it Savcı Bey.
Either Bala or I am going to
have to live it through.
You decide that.
You decide whose heart will burn.
- I won't kill my brother.
- States need blood to shed.
States need...
blood to shed.
Aygül.
My beautiful girl.
Tomorrow is going to be like doomsday.
Savcı will want to be the Bey.
We are going to resist.
You should know that Dündar Bey
will probably be against us.
I know that this is going to be hard
for you.
You can just sit back if you wish.
Mother.
The conquerer of Kulucahisar Osman
Bey deserves to be the Bey.
Whoever tries to take this right
away from him...
will find me against them.
Thank you Aygül, thank you.
I don't have anything to lose.
I'd rather die...
to let them override Osman Bey's right.
We are like sisters with Bala.
If my Bala is standing up with Osman
Bey...
I will support her too.
Mashallah, my girls.
Mashallah.
Tomorrow...
they will come to take your sword.
They will gird on...
your valuable sword.
Who do you want?
Tell me, my Bey.
Tell Abdurrahman...
his last...
duty.
We have a lot to do, Abdurrahman Ghazi!
My Bey...
The end is near.
I want everyone to...
know my decision.
You should know so that
you can act like it.
When
Ertuğrul Ghazi, son of Süleyman Shah...
give his life relic...
Osman, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi, I...
will take his Beyship relic.
We'll go to Ertuğrul Ghazi's tribe to
take his sword and Beyship relic.
We won't stand back
whoever we come across.
Your command, my Bey.
- Where's Dündar Bey?
- He knew we were coming, my Bey.
Won't you stay by me, brother?
I'll stay here, brother.
I'll see that if you draw sword...
to my father's friend Bamsı Bey, aunt
Selcan, Aygül and Bala...
to take the sword of my father.
Osman Bey is coming!
Until victory or death!
Brother!
I'm here! I'm here!
Brothers...
your brother is here...
one step closer and...
I'll cut your head off.
Ertuğrul Bey...
is dying...
I'm the Bey of here...
and this state belongs to me!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com